https://labriutemeals.com/travel-kosher-meals/terms-conditions/

Travel
Terms. Refunds. Privacy.
Contact
Terms. Refunds. Privacy.
FREE EMERGENCY MEAL PLANNING
TALK to our Experts!
Recent BLOG Posts
April 10, 2017
Letter from Bahrain: A Jew at the Arab table
Read More...
pinterest
TERMS & CONDITIONS:
Welcome to LaBriute. Please read the following Terms of use and disclaimer carefully before using or finalizing an order with LaBriutemeals. This Agreement is an agreement between you and Labriute Meals .com that states the terms and conditions under which you may use the Site and receive the Labriute Meals .com service, which includes processing and delivery of product orders. Note that special terms for corporate depot and for Labriute Meals .com Corporate Services customers are contained at the end of this Agreement and where applicable those terms supplement or to the degree that they are inconsistent, supersede these terms. Your use of Labriute Meals service and the Site constitutes your agreement to the terms and conditions set forth below. If you do not agree with all of the terms and conditions, do not use the Site or the Labriute Meals Service. If you have any questions about this Agreement or the Site please call Customer Service and a Team Member will assist you. Labriute Meals products and services are backed by a 100% customer satisfaction guarantee. If you are dissatisfied for any reason, please call us at 1-732-905-1555 or contact us via e-mail at meals@labriutemeals.com
You can place an order anytime 24/7, orders must be received up to one week before your delivery date. Available delivery windows and associated delivery charges will be shown as you proceed through the ordering process. You can modify an existing order by contacting us via Email or calling our Customer Service at 732-905-1555, However, modified orders are subject to price changes and a change of a delivery date may not guarantee the availability of your desired items and you may cancel an order at any time (excluding if the order has been already shipped out). Cancellation of an order after the required cut off time (same day that the order was placed) will result in a restocking and cancellation fee according to the policy below.
Customer’s Note: Please provide a valid address and telephone number for deliveries. We will not be held accountable for orders that have not been able to be delivered due to closed businesses or customers not available at the location to receive the delivery. Please make arrangements to pick up your package if it is left with your doorman (LaBriutemeals will not be held accountable if packages are left and sign for by your doorman and given to you at a later time)
Shipping Policy:
We ship M-F. We do not ship on weekends, National or Jewish Holidays.
Shipping : Is calculated based on your delivery zip code.  WE SHIP ANYWHERE IN THE USA and APO Addresses. Special shipping arrangements can be made for ALASKA & HAWAII.
Order Cancellation will result in a restocking fee equal to the sum of 25% of the total dollar amount of your order.
Returns &  Exchange policy. If you are dissatisfied with an item that you ordered, you may return it before the cut-off time (7 business days after the order has been delivered). Once the returned merchandise is received a credit will be issued. The time credit is issued depends on the financial institution you use.
Restocking Fee: A restocking of 25% will be deducted off the total dollar amount of your returned items.  LaBriutemeals does not credit shipping fees on returns.
Damaged/Spoiled Claims: If your order arrives damaged or spoiled a report must be made by the customer via email only before the required cutoff time (24 hours from the delivery time), When filing for a damaged claim you must provide your order, tracking number and a picture has to be submitted in the email, the items also must be sent back to us in order to file the claim no exceptions. Claims will not be accepted after 24 hours from the delivery time. A claim will be filed by one of our customer representatives and you will received a decision between 3 to 5 business days after the claim has been made.
Missing or Wrong Items: If something is missing from your order, please call our Customer Service department at 1-732-905-1555 or email  meals@labriutemeals.com within 24 Hours after the order has been delivered, otherwise we are not held liable to orders detailed missing or damaged products. In the case of inclement weather or unforeseen delivery complications, it may be necessary to make adjustments to our delivery schedule, which will cause us to suspend chosen delivery dates and times. If there will be a significant delay, a customer service representative may call or e-mail you to let you know the status of your delivery time. If your destination delivery location (i.e., street, avenue, etc.) or day is inaccessible, rendering us unable to make the delivery, we will contact you to determine the best alternate location and/or date.
Transaction Security: Our Site encrypts your credit card and bank account numbers prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. You can update your account information by  calling  732-905-1555. Please review our Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to the Labriute Meals  Site and use of the Labriute Meals  Service, to understand our practices. Acceptable Use Policy You are solely responsible for any and all acts and omissions that occur under your account or password, and you agree not to engage in unacceptable use of the
Labriute Meals  Service, which includes, without limitation, use of the Labriute Meals  Service to: (a) disseminate or transmit unsolicited messages, chain letters, or unsolicited commercial e-mail; (b) disseminate or transmit material that, to a reasonable person, may be abusive, obscene, pornographic, defamatory, harassing, grossly offensive, vulgar, threatening, or malicious; (c) disseminate or transmit files, graphics, software, or other material that actually or potentially infringes the copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, or other intellectual property right of any person; (d) create a false identity or otherwise attempt to mislead any person as to the identity or origin of any communication; (e) export, re-export, or permit downloading of any message or content in violation of any export or import law, regulation, or restriction of the United States and its agencies and authorities, or without all required approvals, licenses, or exemptions; (f) interfere with, disrupt, or attempt to gain unauthorized access to other accounts on the Labriute Meals  Service or any other computer network; (g) disseminate or transmit viruses, Trojan horses, or any other malicious code or program; or (h) engage in any other activity deemed by Labriute Meals  to be in conflict with the spirit or intent of this Agreement.
Warranty Disclaimer; Limitation of Liability;
Indemnification YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT USE OF THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE, THE SITE, AND THE INTERNET IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE, THE SITE, AND ITS CONTENTS ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, LABRIUTE MEALS  DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, WITH RESPECT TO THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE, THE SITE, OR ITS CONTENTS OR WITH RESPECT TO ANY INFORMATION, SERVICES, AND PRODUCTS PROVIDED THROUGH OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE; LABRIUTE MEALS  DOES NOT ADOPT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY MANUFACTURER OR MERCHANT OF ANY SUCH INFORMATION, SERVICE, OR PRODUCTS. LABRIUTE MEALS  MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND AS TO THE AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY, OR CONTENT OF ANY INFORMATION, SERVICES, OR PRODUCTS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE OR THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICES.LABRIUTE MEALS DOES NOT WARRANTS THAT THE FUNCTIONS PROVIDED BY THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE, OR THAT THIS SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE IS FREE FROM VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. NEITHER LABRIUTE MEALS  NOR ANY OF ITS DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SHAREHOLDERS, AFFILIATES, AGENTS, REPRESENTATIVES, THIRD-PARTY INFORMATION PROVIDERS, MERCHANTS, OR LICENSORS (COLLECTIVELY, “LABRIUTE MEALS  PARTIES”) SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, COMPENSATORY, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES; LOSS OF DATA, INCOME, OR PROFIT; OR LOSS OR DAMAGE TO PROPERTY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE SITE, THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE, OR THE INTERNET. LABRIUTE MEALS ’S LIABILITY SHALL BE LIMITED TO PROVIDING YOU WITH A REFUND FOR ANY PRODUCT THAT IS RETURNED. YOU’RE SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY HEREUNDER SHALL BE FOR YOU TO DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THE LABRIUTE MEALS  SERVICE AND TO TERMINATE THIS AGREEMENT.LABRIUTE MEALS  RESERVES THE RIGHT TO LIMIT YOUR ORDER OR THE QUANTITY OF A SPECIFIC PRODUCT YOU MAY ORDER. BECAUSE SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES OR OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, IN SUCH STATES AND JURISDICTIONS LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
The material in the Site is provided for lawful purposes only. Labriute Meals makes no representation that these materials are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you use the Site from other locations, you are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. Price and availability information is subject to change without notice. You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold Labriute meals Parties harmless from any and all suits, actions, legal or administrative proceedings, claims, demands, damages, liabilities, and expenses, including attorney’s fees and costs, arising in connection with a violation of this Agreement by you or through use of your account Miscellaneous Termination. This Agreement is effective upon your acceptance as set forth herein and shall continue in full force and effect until terminated. Labriute meals  may suspend or terminate this Agreement or the Labriute meals  Service or remove or disable access to any portion of the Labriute meals Service at any time for any reason with or without notice to you. You may terminate this Agreement and your Labriute Meals Service at any time for any reason by delivering notice in the manner provided below, which termination will be effective the day notice is received or such later date specified in the notice. Labriute Meals reserves the right to collect fees and charges incurred before you cancel your Labriute meals Service. In addition, you are responsible for any charges incurred to third-party vendors or content providers prior to your cancellation Notices. Labriute meals may give notice to you of a change in this Agreement, a change in the Labriute meals Fee Schedule, and any other matter through a general posting on the Labriute Meals Site, by electronic mail, or by conventional mail to your address contained in the Customer Registration Data. You may give notice to Labriute Meals  by telephone at 732-905-1555 , email meals@labriutemeals.com or by conventional mail to: Labriute Meals  520 James Street unit 1C Lakewood, NJ 08701
Privacy Policy. We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
What This Privacy Policy Covers:
This Privacy Policy covers our site treatment of personally identifiable information that our site collects when you are on it, and when you use our site services.
This policy also covers our site treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us or that we may collect on a partner’s site.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that our site does not own or control, or to people that our site does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
Our site collects personally identifiable information when you submit an order.
We also automatically receive and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookies information and the page you requested.
We use information for three general purposes:
To customize the content, you see.
To fulfill your requests for certain products and services.
To contact you about specials and new products.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information and Preferences
You may request deletion of your account by email us, and confirm your choice to terminate the account.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Security
Your Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
We use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Questions or Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions please email us at Meals@labriutemeals.com.
Terms. Refunds. Privacy.
Labriute Meals
520 James Street,
Lakewood, NJ 08701
732.905.1555
meals@labriutemeals.com
How can we help?
Follow us on:
